Boss.
Where are you?
D-Did you find Qibao?
I'm fine.
You didn't call the police, did you?
I-I didn't call them.
Did you see the kidnapper?
He didn't show his face.
He just made me leave 200,000.
And told me to keep raising money.
No, Boss, I...
I told you, he's got to be a scammer.
Stall him for now.
And then...
I'll go find Chu Feng, Qin Mo, and the others.
Give me an address.
I'll bring them to find you.
But he has Siqi's bag and hat.
I have no choice but to believe him.
I'll just have to put up this restaurant...
as collateral.
However much I can raise...
is what it'll have to be.
I mean, how can you fight these ruthless thugs alone?
Listen to me, just give me an address first.
Your safety is what matters.
I've weathered all kinds of storms in my life.
Don't worry about me.
Hello?
Bos--
The boss has been so wise her whole life,
how can she be acting so foolish now?
She cares too much to think straight.
She cares too much about her daughter.
She thinks money...
can save her daughter's life.
The thing is, we don't know where Qibao is either.
And Boss Bai is acting so impulsively.
What on earth are we going to do?
Come up with an idea, quick!
He Siqi was kidnapped by Guo Yi.
But it's not the same group extorting Bai Ruifen.
This is a textbook case-within-a-case.
We need to sort out our priorities.
I don't care if it's a case-within-a-case.
I want to save Qibao right now.
Captain Chu, Sun Bo just sent word.
He found Guo Yi's address.
It's at Nanzhuang Beili.
Come on, let's go!
Yu Tianfang, get out.
I'm not getting out even if you kill me.
I-I promise.
I-I won't interfere with your operation.
I'll just sit in the car.
Here.
Your favorite buckwheat noodles.
Why so down?
You sick?
Disgusted by me?
No.
I...
I'm just... t-too hungry.
Can you untie me?
I promise.
I won't run, I swear.
My wife...
used to really love the noodles I made too.
What are you smiling at?
I'm severely allergic to buckwheat noodles.
You killed Ma Xiaojun.
And now you're killing me.
You'll have two lives on your hands.
You won't get away either.
A bite of noodles can kill you?
You're trying to outsmart me again.
Look.
First, I get a red rash.
Then I can't breathe.
Finally, cardiac arrest.
And then, death.
No.
You can't die.
Dying would let Chen Dahui off too easy.
If you don't want me to die,
take me to a hospital.
No way.
I know...
there are anti-inflammatories.
I absolutely won't let you die.
I'll go get medicine for you.
I'll go buy you medicine right now.
Trying to die, huh?
I won't let you die that easily.
I'm going to torment you slowly.
This is the place.
Police! Freeze!
Captain Chu.
Surprised?
If you hadn't tried to be so smart,
I wouldn't have put you in here.
Realize your mistake now?
Admit you were wrong,
and I'll go buy you medicine.
Even if I freeze to death,
I will never admit I'm wrong to you.
Fine.
You've got guts.
Then enjoy yourself in here.
I didn't see anything.
I don't know you.
Bro,
please don't kill me.
Take whatever you want.
It was you.
You deliberately ran over my wife.
You caused her miscarriage.
And now she's in a vegetative state.
How can you make up for that?
I don't know.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I was going after her...
I meant to hit her boyfriend.
You animal.
She's the real culprit.
If I had hit her,
your wife and child would be fine, right?
I really want to kill this bastard.
But my upbringing won't let me do that.
So I'm giving you this chance.
You decide.
Whether to kill him,
or spare him.
Didn't you say buckwheat noodles would kill you?
Then die!
That Chen Dahui
is just a scammer.
A scammer!
Let me finish you off.
Didn't you say it was an accident?
I really wanted to believe it was an accident.
But you're just scum.
How dare you bite the hand that feeds you.
I have no choice but to kill you.
So you're not dead.
You almost got me killed!
Qin Mo!
Call for help, quick!
Requesting backup.
We have a fatality in the logistics freezer area.
Siqi!
Call an ambulance!
He Siqi!
Qibao!
Tianfang!
Siqi!
Qibao!
Hold on!
Let's go, get out!
It'll be over soon.
Let's go.